I'm called to order the Reggers here at the meeting of my city council from Monday, April 3rd 2023.
On two proclamation declaring april 16th-23 as first assembly
of God, Centennial Recognition. I'll read a little bit up here first assembly
and God Church was established in January 23rd 2023 to provide hope
for the people who are northeastern Oklahoma
And they have done that successfully over last 100 years
and another good youth program out there.
There are a lot of kids in this community growing up, I remember they had
royal rangers that met their ones at the kid not go
into them sometimes but very active in our communities
They do lots things so
This recognition as well deserve it
We're looking for emotion to take
Hi.
Number three, proclamation declaring April 20th-23 as sexual assault awareness months
hi.
and request for signage in the park.
So this will be Berkeley Allery,
his Inert is 4-H leaders at Grett
so I'm gonna start a little bit here
particularly as started to river you parked clean up
him with mom
His parents
but he organizes us right?
Yeah
And Berkeley even done it
For couple years
Yes
It's been going on since January of 2021
that we initially started this
It was over
Martin Luther King Jr
That weekend
And so my parents and I
started out by looking at what
We could do
So,
decided to pick up
trash in our community
And pretty soon after
4-H came
with a
grant
To allow us
to take on
more projects
And so we've been going
On pretty steadily over the past
two years
We sent me Mr. Baker from
The Spoonville Records
Reach out
To
Allow us
Take in a $1,000 donation
That would allow
Us
When you are
We have a great man
Expand
Our
And so
One of the things that we
Were going to
Requests an
Unfortunately Mr. Baker
Prince
Here tonight as he had
But one
Of
The
Things That
To
Request
Is
For
Signage
At
To
Part
Knowledge
Partnership
Between
These smooth-roll records and the report we've heard from you may be playing out,
And it would work. The aforementioned word that for each has also done in supporting
I forgot another major thing.
So here is a writer for, on years about art day which did already pass that was March 26th
But also in year it's April and May so On April 6th
You will be having an appointment at the age 28
And then you will be having a list going to request that the city would help
To publicize this and we also want
Thank for Mayer because in our last point of day it put out
The date is one or more largest
I think that's what we have.
So, I'm thinking Melinda will
We'll just help us promote
Then Kevin back here he has over a parks
You have anything to say on this Kevin?
So do you need us taking any kind of action
On signage or something that's up and then
And I don't know if we can see it by having a question for Berkeley
I'd like me to ask him what he has.
He went, lots times
It was just happened as parents showed
But they would've had them
And did it with anybody else showing up
So I do applaud you for that as well and if there's anything we can help
On all my hand to helping anyone
The presentation was about the percentage
If somebody is still in high school
Only 4 years
Some kids these days spend other time
And inside playing video games and you're leading the way
So keep on.
I know there are a lot of people coming up
Going around town right now
You inspired us all that, so thank
Because if your efforts continue to do it without
Help sometimes, spend some time other
Thank for each of those.
These two will take care
Number nine
Number twenty three dash 20
Receiving transferring and expanding
The MCB, the S U B
Taho insurance
Recovery check
46 thousand two hundred fifty dollars in seven cents
And minus C bb fund money is a thirty-thousand seventy
$700 to replace
To pay for that
So
I don't think they get to different conferences and tourism
Maybe
No, there was no one
But i'm shocked by a new Taho for fifty thousand dollars
Oh
Sorry.
What we're excited about this
Number ten my little public library mid year update
These girls are always like on top of it
I'm always excited to hear what they have to say
We're going make a motion that we go ahead and open
That now
About the city of Oster gonna be here then
Berkeley will be
Thank my granddaughter
Just kind couple your programs
Yeah, she loves it
These two do amazing job
We're very lucky to have them with after passion
And a lot of what you see and everything that they are doing
They work hard
To make sure the main jobs
Right in grants getting grant
I know whenever i call about
The scams we were going on
That had some elderly citizens who recall me, one other something
We could do and you two were the first to
I thought of
You're like yep we are already on it
So worked out great
Thankyou
Hello
The city of myem a commission agreement for ad cells at
Atthe Miami Community facilities authority MTFA stadium
MCFA has in
The past had various companies that worked on selling
Appetitments and sweets for them
We've not have one
Any company who was actively involved in doing
That a couple of years now
So the three partners
Comprise MCFA
Decided at least two of
Thought we can sell some
Of those ads
We've had some sweets
So we have
Some sweet sold
We haven't
Not real recently but what this does is it allows
Any of the three partners to
Actively participate in
Lazing money for MCFA
And they get a commission
For doing that
We'll see if the three of
The partners equally
So while we say
Of myem itself has not sold any
Those
We want to enter into
The same agreement that
Others are entering
Into
If somebody from city
Were two
Self one be ads or sell
A sweet
And I'm at MCFA
Has a fairly stout budget
They need to meet
We have some major expenses coming up for
The scoreboard
Peter system and i can't tell you the technology of all this
But it's going
It is getting that brought
Of today
So it's important that we get
Get these ads sold
To the sweet
For a motion to accept
To approve agreement
Is there a limit
How many advertising
Soldiers is
There
Because
That is available
One of the things that they have been in
The past
They've had banner sales
Which are much cheaper
Very
Much cheaper
And so
Some would be
Sales
Add space on
The scoreboard itself has gone
Unsold
Because some
So they are looking at
And the discussion has been about
Whether or not to eliminate
The banner sales
To try and help pick up
Sales on
Scoreboard
There's some production going along
Yes
I think that
They came provide their own
The MCFA will do it for them
But there's an additional expense
I need to stay here
They're on the interview
Yeah, you don't be a good thing
Or at 223-02
Amending Section 24-28
Division 1 of Article 2
Chapter 234
And then
In 13
We, the emergency calls
To enact this
Or not
So 23-02
And make an ineffective
Meal
Correct
Conflict of interest
The disclosure form
The last week
That the idea is to help us identify
Where there's a potential conflict of interest
Maybe we can do better job on catching them all
So
But anyway, it will
Help facilitate
Helpus
To facilitate
Getting pulled out
Of what other actions you may be taking
And it's for your protection
As well as for the city's protection
One of those thoughts about
The questions on that like motion to a brief
Other new business if any, which is a residence
Of the posting in this agenda
I would just
Like the command
Those in community
Mark Lee
And there's other people doing it
In any arresting team today
Was out and cleaned up
Peestreet
That was quite a pile of stuff
They cleaned about their
It really good that they got involved
I know red collar for Prina
Got all the way to them
They don't like those
They're going to have a court day
With their employees
To physically help efforts
So hopefully that will kind of
Paralyze mother, business in the doing as well
But again
It just takes
One 14 year old
Get something rolling and it gets contagious
My logic is we need
And I would like for us to talk about this
A feature
Planning session
Maybe we have a council in mayor
Lead something
In our districts and
We've got lead by example for some other people
So that's not the one thing about later
I'll tell you